女士们先生们 接下来是万众期待的表演
Ladies and gents, this is the moment you've waited for.
黑暗中不断摸索 辛勤汗水汇聚成河
Been searching in the dark, your sweat soaking through the floor.
久埋心底的渴望无法再次忽视
And buried in your bones there's an ache that you can't ignore.
深呼吸 保持清醒 将一切顾虑抛诸脑后
Taking your breath, stealing your mind. And all that was real is left behind.
别抗拒 它为你而生 何不为它而活
Don't fight it, it's coming for you, running at ya.
就是现在 别去顾虑未来如何
It's only this moment, don't care what comes after.
心心念念的 它近在咫尺了
Your fever dream, can't you see it getting closer.
放飞自己 此刻让内心去掌控
Just surrender 'cause you feel the feeling taking over.
那是火 是自我 是奔涌而出的激情时刻
It's fire, it's freedom, it's flooding open.
它像信仰一样指引着你去释放自己
It's a preacher in the pulpit and you'll find devotion.
束缚你的高墙 已然倒塌
There's something breaking at the brick of every wall it's holding all that you know,
何不与我们同行?
so tell me do you wanna go?
那里没有异样的眼光
Where it's covered in all the colored lights.
那里都是为自己而战的人
Where the runaways are running the night.
一切皆有可能 你感受到了吗
Impossible comes true, it's taking over you.
噢 这就是最佳表演
Oh, this is the greatest show.
调动全身的激情 传奇永不落幕
We light it up, we won't come down.
精彩将持续上演
And the sun can't stop us now.
它真的实现了 你感受到了吗
Watching it come true, it's taking over you.
噢 这就是最佳表演
Oh, this is the greatest show.
这有你向往的一切 这有你需要的所有
It's everything you ever want. It's everything you ever need.
现在它近在咫尺 这就是你的归宿
And it's here right in front of you. This is where you wanna be.
这有你向往的一切 这有你需要的所有
It's everything you ever want. It's everything you ever need.
现在它近在咫尺 这就是你的归宿
And it's here right in front of you. This is where you wanna be.
这有你向往的一切 这有你需要的所有
It's everything you ever want It's everything you ever need.
现在它近在咫尺
And it's here right in front of you.
这就是你的归宿
This is where you wanna be.
这有你向往的一切
It's everything you ever want.
这有你需要的所有
It's everything you ever need.
现在它近在咫尺
And it's here right in front of you.
我明白 非常感谢 杰弗里先生 谢谢
I understand, yes. Thank you very much, Mr. Jeffrey. Thank you.
今天晚些时候我会付钱给你的
You have the money by the end of the day.
我们走
Let's go.
菲尼亚斯 快点 要不然就误掉火车了
Phineas, hurry up. We are gonna miss the train.
站直
Stand up straight.
把这些污渍都擦掉
Wipe that muck off.
拿起来
Pick it up.
手臂伸出来 手肘朝外
Arm extended, elbow out.
小口的喝 别喝出声音
Sip, and never slurp.
拿起来 手臂伸出来
Begin here, arm extended...
手肘朝外
elbow out.
保持杯子的高度 慢慢放下
Keep your cup level. Low your cup.
要不要再来一次
Shall we do it again?
手臂伸出来 手肘朝外 要优雅
Arm extended, elbow out. Gracefully.
查丽蒂 过来
Charity, come here.
看看你的裙子 爸妈是教你这么表现的么
Your dress. Is this how we have taught you to behave?
是我的错 先生
It's my fault, sir.
我逗她笑了
I made her laugh.
那真是谢谢你的诚实了
Well, thank you for your honesty.
离我的女儿远点
Stay away from my daughter.
- 你怎么出来的 - 从窗户爬出来的
- How did you get out? - The window.
我爸叫我去把书念完
Father is sending me to finishing school.
不知道自己以后会成什么样子
I don't know what my future will be.
我知道
I do.
闭上双眼 我看见
I close my eyes and I can see.
世界正等待着我
The world that's waiting up for me.
那便是属于我的地方
That I call my own.
穿过茫茫黑暗 穿过那扇门
Through the dark, through the door
穿越那无人企及之处
Through where no one's been before
却如家一般温馨
but it feels like home.
他们会说 会说那真的是太可怕了
They can say, they can say it all sounds crazy.
他们会说 会说我失去了理智
They can say, they can say I've lost my mind.
我不在乎 毫不在意 就当我疯了吧
I don't care, I don't care, so call me crazy.
我们可以生活在自己创造的世界里了
We can live in a world that we design
因为每晚我躺在床上
'Cause every night I lie in bed.
脑海中满是缤纷的思绪
The brightest colors fill my head.
无数的梦让我浮想联翩
A million dreams are keeping me awake.
我在想世界会变成什么样
I think of what the world could be.
我将会看到怎样的一个精彩的世界
A vision of the one I see.
无数的梦想交织在一起
A million dreams is all it's gonna take.
将由我们编织成完美的世界
A million dreams for the world we're gonna make.
他们会说 会说那真的是太可怕了
They can say, they can say it all sounds crazy.
他们会说 会说我失去了理智
They can say, they can say we've lost our minds.
查丽蒂
Charity!
我不在乎 毫不在意 就当我疯了吧
I don't care, I don't care if they call us crazy.
逃向我们自己创造的世界
run away to a world that we designed.
每晚我躺在床上
Cause every night I lie in bed.
脑海中满是缤纷的思绪
The brightest colors fill my head.
无数的梦让我浮想联翩
A million dreams are keeping me awake.
我在想世界会变成什么样
I think of what the world could be.
我将会看到怎样的一个精彩的世界
A vision of the one I see.
无数的梦想交织在一起
A million dreams is all it's gonna take.
不
No.
将由我们编织成完美的世界
A million dreams for the world we're gonna make.
卖报 上面有全世界最棒的新闻
Newspapers. Amazing stories from around the world.
无数的梦让我浮想联翩
A million dreams are keeping me awake.
我在想世界会变成什么样
I think of what the world could be.
我将会看到怎样的一个精彩的世界
A vision of the one I see.
无数的梦想交织在一起
A million dreams is all it's gonna take.
将由我们编织成完美的世界
A million dreams for the world we're gonna make.
快来加入我们 建造伟大的美国铁路吧
Come join the Great American Railroad.
包三餐 包住宿
Three meals a day. A roof over your head.
报酬丰厚 来赚一笔吧
Fair and ample wages. Come, make your fortune.
来看看广阔的美国平原吧
See the open plains of America.
机会等待着你 先生 一起去建造铁路吧
Opportunity awaits you sir, out on the rails.
先生 我知道我不是很有钱
Sir I, I know I don't come from much
但是我会好好照顾你的女儿
but I will take care of your daughter
我会让她过上富足的幸福生活
and I will give her a life as grand as this one.
再见 妈妈
Goodbye, mother.
她会回来的
She'll be back.
她迟早会厌倦跟你在一起 一无所有的日子
Sooner or later she will get tired of your life of having nothing
她就会想着回来的
and she will keep running back home.
每晚我躺在床上
Every night I lie in bed.
脑海中满是缤纷的思绪
The brightest colors fill my head.
无数的梦让我浮想联翩
A million dreams are keeping me awake.
我在想世界会变成什么样
I think of what the world could be.
我将会看到怎样的一个精彩的世界
A vision of the one I see.
无数的梦想交织在一起
A million dreams is all it's gonna take.
将由我们编织成完美的世界
A million dreams for the world we're gonna make.
不管它是大还是小
However big, however small.
让我融为其中
Let me be part of it all.
一起分享着你我的梦想
Share your dreams with me.
你或许是对的 又或是错的
You may be right, you may be wrong.
你带着我一起
But say that you'll bring me along.
向着眼前的世界前进
To the world you see.
闭着眼睛 用心感受
To the world I close my eyes to see.
我闭上双眼
I close my eyes to see
每晚我躺在床上
Cause every night I lie in bed.
脑海中满是缤纷的思绪
The brightest colors fill my head.
无数的梦想激励我前行
A million dreams are keeping me awake.
无数的梦想
A million dreams, a million dreams.
我在想世界会变成什么样
I think of what the world could be.
我将会看到怎样的一个精彩的世界
A vision of what I see.
无数的梦想交织在一起
A million dreams is all it's gonna take.
将由我们编织成完美的世界
A million dreams for the world we're gonna make.
为了我们将创造的这美好世界
For the world we're gonna make.
- 史密斯先生 - 是我
- Mr. Smith? - Yeah.
来看看这个
Have a look at this, here?
好的我看到了
Yes, yes, I see it.
谢谢 查默斯 这个可以
Thank you, Chalmers, that will do.
先生 我是菲尼亚斯·泰勒·巴纳姆
Sir. Phineas Taylor Barnum.
如果愿意听我讲讲的话 先生
If I may sir,
我觉得我有才华 很有想法
I believe I have skills and ideas...
不应该把自己限制在操作加法机上
that go well beyond counting numbers into an adding machine.
我在报纸上读到了这个德国人的故事 他叫利林塔尔
I have read about this German fellow, Lilienthal...
他发明了一种滑翔机
I believe he's developed a glider
能把人送上天 先生
that could take a man in the air, sir.
这样很棒的
Isn't that amazing?
如果能把这个技术投入实际运用
I mean, if you were to apply that to this business,
将是具有革命性的
it would be revolutionary.
先生 请注意 你们都被解雇了
Gentlemen. Can I have your attention? You are all dismissed.
破产了
Bankrupt?
我听说公司有很多商船呢
I thought the company had a dozen trading ships.
是啊 沉到南中国海的海底去了
Yes, at the bottom of the South China Seas.
刮了台风 全沉了
A typhoon sank them all.
船只登记
- 抓住你了 - 你在这儿呢
- Tinker it. - Oh, you're in for it.
- 嘿 - 我的天 你回家早了啊
- Hey. - Oh God. You are home early.
你看看这个
And until further notice.
我是不觉得你愿意干那份工作
Oh I didn't think you were along for that job.
别的工作也不怎么感兴趣啊
Or any job apparently.
那让我们在一起的生活更有意思了
That's what makes our life together so exciting.
夏瑞蒂
Charity.
- 我答应给你的生活 不是这个样子的 - 但我想要的都有了啊
- This isn't the life I promised you. - But I have everything I want.
- 但这生活没有意思啊 - 这两个女孩是你的什么人
- What about the magic? - What do you call those two girls?
孩子们 看谁来了
Hey, you partners, look who.
爸爸
Daddy!
- 来 - 你给我带了礼物么
- Come here. - Did you bring a present?
什么礼物
Present, for what?
- 我的生日啊 - 你的什么
- For my birthday. - Your what?
- 我的生日 - 这不是你的生日
- My birthday. - It's not your birthday.
不过没事 我这有一份礼物
Okay, I do have a present.
但这可不是普通的礼物
But not just any present. Oh no.
这可是最棒的生日礼物
The most amazing birthday present ever.
这台巧夺天工的机器最早
This extraordinary machine was originally
是400年前由列奥纳多·达·芬奇制造的
created by Leonardo Da Vinci 400 years ago.
但是机器的蓝图消失了好几个世纪
But the blueprints have been lost for centuries,
直到上周 那是一个风暴交加的夜晚
until just last week, on a stormy night...
一辆沉没海盗船的残骸 冲上了楠塔基特岛的岸边
when a sunken pirate ship washed up on the shores of Nantucket.
人们发现骷髅 财宝
They found skeletons and treasures...
还有由"JW商业公司"发现的一幅机器蓝图
and the blueprints were recovered by none other than JW Mercantile.
机器的蓝图在我这停留的时间不长
The blueprints crossed my desk very briefly...
但我试着将它记了下来
but I managed to commit them to memory...
如果我记得没错的话
and if I had remembered correctly...
生日快乐 卡洛琳
Happy birthday, Caroline.
这是一台许愿机器 你对它许愿
This is a wishing machine. You tell it your wishes...
它会记录下你们的愿望 一直到愿望实现
and it keeps them safe until they come true.
就算你们忘了 那些愿望还是会留在这里
Even if you forget them, they are always there.
- 我能许愿么 - 走上前来 开始吧
- Can I tell a wish? - Step right up. Go ahead.
- 我希望能嫁给圣诞老人 - 你这个愿望好
- I wish to marry Santa Clause. - That is a good wish.
我想要一双芭蕾舞鞋
I wish for ballet slippers.
你这个愿望也不错
Hey, that's a good wish too.
你有什么愿望么 妈咪
What is your wish, Mommy?
我希望
I wish...
我们能像这样 永远幸福
for happiness like this forever.
你们两位
For you and you...
还有你的父亲 都幸福
and for your father.
- 无聊 - 无聊
- Boring. - Boring?
幸福的日子怎么会无聊呢
Since when is happiness ever been boring?
每晚我躺在床上
Every night I lie in bed.
脑海中满是缤纷的思绪
The brightest colors fill my head.
无数的梦想激励我前行
A million dreams are keeping me awake.
我在想世界会变成什么样
I think of what the world could be.
我将会看到怎样的一个精彩的世界
A vision of the one I see.
无数的梦想交织在一起
A million dreams is all it's gonna take.
将由我们编织成完美的世界
A million dreams for the world we're gonna make.
金融危机
山羊的价格上升了 五花肉的价格下跌了
The goat prices go up, so the pork bellies go down.
- 查尔斯 我们走 - 怎么了
- Charles, we're leaving. - Huh?
银行只借钱给有钱人
This bank only wants to lend money to people with money.
你看什么看
What are you looking at Flop Doodle?
巴纳姆先生
Mr. Barnum.
你提出的这个项目风险很大 而且有点奇怪
This venture you propose is risky and somewhat bizarre.
我这个项目其实挺好的 先生 人们只是不愿意相信罢了
It's a good bet, it's what it is. Sir, people don't wanna admit it...
但是那些异国情调的和恐怖的展品能吸引观众
but they are fascinated with the exotic and the...
我主要关注的是这个
is why we stare at it.
银行需要你提供大量的抵押物作担保
The bank is going to need substantial collateral.
当然 不然也不会借钱给我了
Of course. I would not suggest otherwise.
我名下有一支商船队 这里是契据及业权
The deed and title to my entire fleet of trading vessels.
为什么银行会借给我们1万美元
Why would a bank loan us 10,000 dollars?
因为我提供给了他们担保物
Because we put up collateral.
但是我们没有什么担保物啊
We don't have any collateral.
当然有的 在南中国海呢
Sure we do. In the South China Seas.
- 南中国海 - 在南中国海海底呢
- In the South China Seas? - Deep in the South China Seas.
我们打算用这笔钱购置什么吗
And what did we buy with this loan?
美国巴纳姆奇物博物馆
Barnum's American Museum of Curiosity.
这是什么博物馆啊
What kind of museum is it?
我们会改造这里
A place to be transported.
在这里人们会看到前所未有的新奇事物
A place where people can see thing they've never seen before.
- 蜡像么 - 对
- Wax figures? - Yeah.
都是欧洲产的
They are all the rage in Europe. Look.
嗓子痛的玛丽亚·安东尼特
Marie Antoinette with the sore throat.
还有拿破仑 过来 看到了么
Napoleon. Come here. You see?
你们已经见过了历史上几个有名的人物了
You have already met some of the most famous folks from the history.
不止是蜡像而已
But they are not all wax.
这位是奥马利先生
This is the Great O'Malley.
戏法之王 擅长瞒天过海
Master of sleight of hand, the king of deception.
- 你看起来可不像魔法师啊 - 我是个贼
- You don't look like a magician. - I am a thief.
很厉害的贼 他偷我手表的时候我抓住他了
A very good thief. I caught him taking my watch.
- 看到了没 - 那有大象
- You see? - An elephant.
- 那可不是普通的大象
Not just any elephant.
我会让你刮目相看的
I'll get you something real nice to say the word.
- 谢谢 - 这玩意可有10吨重
- Thank you. - Oh yeah. This is a ten ton bulls...
从非洲平原弄来的
straight from the plains of Africa.
看那个
And, look at that.
- 世界上最高的长颈鹿 - 我能顺着它的腿爬上去么
- The tallest giraffe in the world. - Can I climb up its leg?
绝对 不行
Absolutely no. OK.
- 我知道现在是个什么情况 - 如果你不知道的话 我会很担心的
- Now, I know how it looks. - If you didn't, I would be worried.
我们要努力一下了 不过...
I mean it just needs a little work..
每个月要还贷的
The loan has to be paid back every month.
我们会还的 需要观众而已
Oh yeah, we're gonna pay. We just need customers.
- 要很多的观众 - 会有的
- Hundreds of them. - We're gonna get them.
巴纳姆美国奇异博物馆
欢迎来到巴纳姆博物馆 参观一小时
Welcome to the Barnum Museum. It is one hour of your time, sir...
这次经历会改变你的一生
but it will change your life.
任意时间均可参观
We have a shows on the hour, every hour.
我喜欢你的裙子
I love your dress.
不推荐胆子小的人去看 但是你们会喜欢上那里的
Surely not for the fainted heart. I can tell you that you'll love it.
戴帽子的顾客半价
Half the price for anyone who is wearing a hat.
就是你了 先生
Ho ho, That's you, sir.
欢迎来到巴纳姆博物馆
Welcome to the Barnum Museum.
真是垃圾
Garbage.
欢迎来到巴纳姆博物馆 顾客呢
Welcome to the Barnum Museum, where everyone...
卖出去多少张票
How many tickets?
- 三张 - 三张?
- Three. - Three?
家庭支出
爸爸
Daddy.
Daddy?
- 你今天有没有卖出去更多的票 - 卖出去一些了
- You sell anymore tickets today? - A few. Yeah.
周五了 大家急着回家
Most of 'em was rushing home, it's Friday.
卖出去一些了
We sold a few.
爸爸 我觉得你的博物馆里死的东西太多了
I think you have too many dead things in your museum daddy.
是么
Do you?
她说得对 我们要一些活的东西
She is right. You need something alive.
- 你们俩去睡吧 - 要一些能引发轰动的东西
- Go to sleep, both of you. - Something sensational.
- 你们用的这个词很大啊 - 那是你用过的词
- That is a big word. - That's your word.
要那些不是填充标本的东西
Something that isn't stuffed.
- 比如美人鱼 - 独角兽
- Like a mermaid. - Or a unicorn.
- 独角兽不存在的 - 美人鱼也不存在的
- Unicorns aren't real. - Well, mermaids aren't real either.
您是格特鲁德·斯特拉顿吧
You must be Gertrude Stratton.
我要找您的儿子
I am looking for your son.
我没有儿子
I don't have a son.
医院的档案上写着 你有一个儿子啊
The hospital record says you do.
是叫查尔斯吧 22岁
Charles, right? Age 22?
查尔斯
Charles.
我是P·T·巴纳姆 愿意为您效劳
P. T Barnum. At your service.
我在组织一个剧团
I'm putting together a show...
需要一位明星演员
and I need a star.
大家会笑话我的
You want people to laugh at me.
不管怎样他们都会笑话你的 至少我们能赚到钱嘛
Well, they are laughing anyway, kid. So, might as well get paid.
我眼前浮现出一位士兵 不 一位将军
I see a soldier. No, a general...
走过舞台 手里拿着剑和枪
riding across the stage with a sword and gun and...
身着最为精致的制服
and the most beautiful uniform ever made.
全世界的人们来到这里
People will come from all over the world
他们不会笑话你
and when they see him they won't laugh.
他们会向你敬礼
They will salute.
需要 奇特之人 浮夸的表演 世界奇人
Wanted! Unique persons, curiosities. Daring acts. Wonders of the world.
看起来怎么样 孩子们
How is it looking girls?
你在找那些怪胎么
Hey. You looking for freaks?
我知道上哪能找到
I know where you can find one of them.
是么
Really?
来吧 孩子们
Come on, girls.
- 你好 - 先生你不能进来
- Hello. - Sir, you can't be here.
很抱歉 唱歌的这位是谁
I'm sorry. Who is doing that singing?
就是你吧
It's you, isn't it?
- 请您离开 先生 - 你真是很有天分...
- Sir, I'll have to ask you to leave. - You are so talented, blessed...
太奇妙了
Extraordinary.
很奇特
Unique.
我甚至能用漂亮这个词来形容你
I would even say 'beautiful'.
先生
Sir,
请不要打扰我
please leave me alone.
他们现在不理解你 但他们以后会的
They don't understand it, but they will.
安 和 W.D. 惠勒
OK. Anne and WD Wheeler.
- 你们是兄妹么 - 是的 先生
Brother and sister?
好的 你们有什么特殊技能么
- Yes sir. - Terrific. And what do you do?
- 我们会玩空中飞人 - 空中飞人
- Trapeze. - Trapeze. OK.
要是你让我们登台演出的话 估计公众反响会不太好
You know, people aren't gonna like it if you put us on the stage.
我就指望着这点呢
Oh, I am counting on it.
世界上最棒的空中飞人 安 和 W.D. 惠勒
- 你的... - 整个身体
- Is this so far your... - Entire body.
不错 不用全部展示给我看了
Fantastic. I don't need to see it.
*纹身男
Tattoo Man Barnum Museum.
*狗男
Dog boy.
我能问问你有多重么
Can I just ask how heavy you are?
能告诉我么
Do you have a number for that?
- 我觉得还是不说比较好 - 我不会说出去的
- I prefer not to say it, but... - Just between you and me.
500磅
500 pounds.
- 750磅? 你是说750磅么 - 750磅
- 750 pounds? Is what you said? - 750 pounds!
*世界上最肥胖的男人
World's heaviest man.
- 你叫什么名字？ - 先生您好 我叫瓦西里·帕洛斯
- What's your name? - Vasily Palvos, sir.
这名字得改一下
Yeah, we are going to change that name.
我觉得你是爱尔兰人
I think you're Irish.
*爱尔兰巨人
Irish Giant.
这阵容绝对够用了
We have a show.
很不错 海报的版面再翻五倍
That's good, but I need it five times bigger.
所有地方都贴上海报
And I want it everywhere.
马车上 火车侧面上 手推车上 墙上
Carriages, sides of trains, trolleys, crates...
牛奶瓶上 满世界都是海报
milk bottles, everywhere they look.
巴纳姆美国博物馆
Barnum's American Museum.
你过得磕磕绊绊
Nice to see you, sir.
一直低着头
You stumble through your days. Got your head hung low.
漫天阴云不散
Your skies' a shade of Grey.
-  如僵尸于迷宫内蹒跚 - 两张票 谢谢
Like a zombie in a maze. - Two, please.
你内心昏沉 但仍可听见希望的呼唤
You're asleep inside But you can shake awake.
因为你只是行尸走肉
'Cause you're just a dead man walking Thinking that's your only option.
以为已别无他选
But you can flip the switch and brighten up your darkest day.
但你可打起精神 点亮你昏暗的世界
Sun is up and the color's blinding. Take the world and redefine it.
太阳升起 光芒明艳
Leave behind your narrow mind. You'll never be the same.
掌控世界 立规定矩
Come alive, come alive.
拓新思路 开始改变
Go and light your light. Let it burn so bright.
觉醒吧 觉醒吧
Reaching up to the sky.
跟着心中的光 让你的世界更加耀眼
And it's open wide. You're electrified.
伸出手 指向天
When the world becomes a fantasy.
看到那广阔无垠 你会动力无限
And you're more than you could ever be.
世界充满梦幻 你会打破桎梏 突破极限
'Cause you're dreaming with your eyes wide open.
因为梦想就在你的眼前
And you know you can't go back again.
过往的生活你绝不再要
To the world that you were living in.
因为梦想就在你的眼前
'Cause you're dreaming with your eyes wide open.
所以觉醒吧
So, come alive!
- 他们等着呢 - 等什么？
- Lettie. They are waiting. - For what?
在等你
- For you. - No.
他们现在还不知道
They don't know it yet,
但他们会爱死你的
but they are gonna love you.
相信我
Trust me.
大拇指汤姆
Tom.
你们上啊
Up, up.
在你眼神中我看见
I see it in your eyes.
你笃信匿影藏形的谎言
You believe that lie. That you need to hide your face.
害怕出现在人们的眼前
Afraid to go outside.
所以你禁锢了自己 但其实大可不必
So you lock the door. But don't you stay that way.
不想生活在阴影里 我们都知道曾经心中所感
No more living in those shadows. You and me, we know how that goes.
一旦看到希望 生活注定会改变
'Cause once you see it, oh you'll never, never be the same.
我们会变得靓丽夺目
We will be the light that's turning.
抬起头勇往直前
Bottle up but keep on shining.
你可以证明自己潜能无边 你不用心惊胆颤
You can prove there's more to you. You cannot be afraid.
觉醒吧 觉醒吧
Come alive, come alive.
跟着心中的光 让你的世界更加耀眼
Go and light your light. Let it burn so bright.
伸出手 指向天
Reaching up to the sky.
看到那广阔无垠 你会动力无限
And it's open wide. You're electrified.
世界充满梦幻
When the world becomes a fantasy.
你会打破桎梏 突破极限
And you're more than you could ever be.
因为梦想就在你的眼前
'Cause we're dreaming with our eyes wide open.
过往的生活
And we know we can't go back again.
你绝不再要
To the world that we were living in.
因为梦想就在你的眼前
'Cause we're dreaming with our eyes wide open.
所以 觉醒吧
So, come alive!
真棒
Bravo.
真是太好了
That was amazing.
- 太好了 - 很棒
- Superb! - Fantastic.
评论对我们太不利了 巴纳姆博物馆 骗子的聚集地
This is bad. The Barnum Museum. A primitive Circus of Humbug.
“罪犯 贪婪"
"Criminal." "Greedy".
马戏团”马戏团这个词我还是很喜欢的
"A circus." I like circus.
这就对了 坏小子们
That's right, bad boy.
你要保护这位长了胡子的小姐么
You are gonna protect the bearded lady?
够了 沃特
Hay... That's enough. Walter.
- 所有人给我立刻进来 - 看他们跑了
- Inside, all! Right? - Look them run.
- 我们可不想你们待在这 - 滚远点
- We do not want your kind here. - Get out of here.
注意了 怪物们 你们的主人在召唤你们呢
That's right, you freaks. Your master's calling.
你说够了吧 这位先生
That's quite enough, sir.
没什么好看的
Nothing more to look at.
我们走喽
At your service.
马上让纽约所有报纸上登出此消息
You print this review in every paper in New York.
下场演出门票半价
Half price ticket to anyone who with it.
巴纳姆博物馆 入场券半价大酬宾
票已售空
Sold out.
来吧 大家都来吧
Come one! Come all!
进来看吧 来吧
Come in! Come on!
所有拥有梦想的人啊
To anyone who's bursting with a dream.
来吧
Come one! Come all!
听到那呼唤声了吧
You hear the call.
寻找奋斗出路的人们啊
To anyone who's searching for a way to break free.
-  释放自我吧！ -  释放自我吧！
Break free! Break free!
世界充满梦幻
When the world becomes a fantasy.
你会打破桎梏 突破极限
And you're more than you could ever be.
因为梦想就在你的眼前
'Cause you're dreaming with your eyes wide open.
过往的生活
And we know we can't go back again.
你绝不再要
To the world that we were living in.
因为梦想就在你的眼前
'Cause we're dreaming with our eyes wide open.
世界充满梦幻
When the world becomes a fantasy.
你会打破桎梏 突破极限
And you're more than you could ever be.
因为梦想就在你的眼前
'Cause you're dreaming with your eyes wide open.
过往的生活
And we know we can't go back again.
你绝不再要
To the world that we were living in.
因为梦想就在你的眼前
'Cause we're dreaming with our eyes wide open.
所以 觉醒吧
So come alive!
觉醒吧
Come alive.
卖花生 卖花生喽
Peanuts. Get your peanuts here.
- 热乎的腌制花生哟 - 给我和这位女士各来一份
- Hot, salted peanuts. - One for me and one for the lady.
奥马利
O'Malley.
哈罗德报社的本内特先生
Ah, Mr. Bennett from the Herald.
又来看表演了吧？
Come to take in another show, huh?
告诉我 巴纳姆先生
Tell me, Mr. Barnum,
你兜售的这些噱头都是假的 难道你不愧疚吗？
does it bother you that everything you're selling is fake?
难道观众的笑声都是假的吗？
Do these smiles seem fake?
这些演员来历并不重要 重要的是观众开心
It doesn't matter where they come from. The joy is real.
所以你是个慈善家喽？
So you are a philanthropist?
夸张一些也不是很大的罪过嘛
Well, hyperbole isn't the worst crime.
人们因想象力受到局限所遭的罪更大一些
Men suffer more from imagining too little than too much.
你这话都能当骗子们的教义了
The creed of a true fraud.
本内特先生 你上次开怀大笑是什么时候的事？
Mr Bennett, when was the last time you smiled?
我说的是真正开心的那种笑
Or had a good laugh? A real laugh.
一个在剧院体验不到娱乐的评论家
A theater critic who can't find joy in the theater.
你说我们俩谁才是骗子呢？
Now who is the fraud?
哦 本内特先生
Oh, Mr. Bennett.
记得上次你评论我的演出时用的那个词吗？
That word you used to describe my show,
我觉得那词用的真棒
has a nice ring to it.
P·T·巴纳姆马戏团
P.T. Barnum's Circus.
这边走
This way.
你不认为我这辈子太容易相信人了吗？
Don't you think there is enough 'blind trust' in my life?
这样的你才有趣 继续往前走 到了
Well, isn't that what makes it fun? Keep coming. Okay.
你准备好了吗?
Are you ready?
- 这个是？ - 是的 就是那个
- Is it? - It is.
我们进去
Come on. Let's go.
推开吧
Push.
海伦 那是给你的
Helen, that's for you.
卡洛琳 这个是给你的
And, Caroline, this is for you.
刚过你父母家的街那边
There is a ballet school right down the street.
有所芭蕾舞学校
Just past your parents' house.
别跟我说你买这个房子只是为了向我父母
Don't tell me you bought this house
炫耀你的成就
just to rub my parents' noses in your success.
不都是这个原因啦
That was not the only reason.
这是我承诺过要给你的生活
This is the life I promised you.
我们跳舞吧
Shall we?
菲尼亚斯
Phin...
这房子是很漂亮 但是我们真的不用...
It's beautiful, but we don't need all of this.
已经25年了
It took me 25 years, but...
欢迎回家 夏瑞蒂·巴纳姆
Welcome home, Charity Barnum.
- 你好 - 巴纳姆来了
- Hello there! - Barnum is in.
那个小伙子是谁？
Hey, sweetie, who is that young man over there?
他是菲利普·卡莱尔 人们都说他是骗子
That is Philip Carlyle. A bit of a scandal, they say.
他上次在伦敦的表演很成功
- His last play was a hit in London. - Play?
人们花好大一笔钱
Pay good money to
就愿意看台上的人叨叨2个小时 他们居然好意思说我是骗子
watch people stand around and talk for two hours, and they call me a con man.
这是什么味啊？ 你闻到了吗？
Ew. What's that smell? Do you smell that?
- 真恶心 这味确实够难闻的 - 我知道了 是花生（谐音P.T巴纳姆的P 讽刺巴纳姆一家）
- Ew, something does smell. - I know what it is. Peanuts.
我已经看到你的未来了
I can see it right now.
你将会是都市芭蕾舞剧历史中最年轻的芭蕾女舞蹈家
"Youngest prima ballerina in the history of the City ballet."
- 我不想跳芭蕾了 - 什么？为什么不想跳了？
- I'm quitting. - What? Why would you quit?
我学的太晚了 永远也别想跟上他们的高度
I started too late. I will never catch up.
卡洛琳 你是舞台上跳的最好的
Caroline, you were the best dancer on that stage.
你觉得我看不出谁有天赋吗？
What? Do you think I can't spot talent?
想跳好芭蕾须数年苦练 跟马戏团不是一回事
Ballet takes years of hard work. It's not like the circus.
坑蒙拐骗是行不通的
You can't just fake it.
她不能放弃 不对 我是说她不该放弃
She can't quit. No. No, I mean... She doesn't.
她只是觉得有人排挤她了而已
She just feels out of place with the other girls.
我也希望如此
Well, I should certainly hope so.
我这辈子可 没见过这么多自以为是的人
I have never seen so many little prima Donnas in my life.
这些自以为是的人
Yes, but those prima Donnas are the most
现在对小卡洛琳来说非常重要
important thing in the world to her right now.
她得学会无视那些人 我小时候就这么干的
She'll learn to ignore them, just like I did.
她不是非得如此
She shouldn't have to.
纽约社会永远不会真心接纳我们
New York society will never accept us.
这些人一天天的 不对我们品头论足
If they did, they'd have to stop judging...
都不知道怎么继续过日子了
and actually do something with their lives.
这事不能往我身上扯
This isn't about me.
你是说这事的起因跟其他的不一样喽？
Oh... So it's different than everything else then?
我只是希望她因是我们家庭的一份子而感到自豪
I just want her to be proud of who she is, of her family.
她很自豪
She is proud.
我们不必非得变成卡莱尔家那样
We don't have to be the Carlyle's.
卡莱尔先生 这部戏是你制作的？
Mr. Carlyle. You produced this play?
是的
Yes I do, indeed.
退票去售票处
Refunds are available at front box office.
- 我是P·T·巴纳姆 - 开马戏团的那个?
- P.T. Barnum. - From the circus?
- 对 你看过我的演出?
Yes. You've been?
天啊 我可没看过 但我见过你的团队成员
God, no. But I've seen the crowds.
人们看完你的演出后都很开心
People leave your show happier than when they came in.
比我的戏有意思多了
Which is much more than I can say from my play.
但你票可不愁卖啊
And yet, you have no trouble selling tickets.
那是因为我的卖点是节操
That's because I'm selling virtue.
我能请你跟我喝一杯吗？
Can I buy you a drink?
我想要争取到高端群众
I want to go after the carriage straight.
加入正剧情节 扩大影响力
Present legitimate acts, expand our appeal...
专门针对那些势利小人
go after the snobs.
你要是知道这帮人多难缠的话就不会...
If you only knew how suffocating they are.
加入我的马戏团吧
So come join our circus.
很明显你在娱乐圈很有眼光
You clearly have a flair for show business.
教我如何吸引更多的关注度
Teach me how to appeal to the highbrows.
你认真的？
Are you serious?
巴纳姆先生 我不能就这么简单地跑到你那加入你的团队
Mr. Barnum, I can not just run off enter into circus.
为什么不行？听着不是挺好么
Why not? Sounds thrilling isn't it?
就当我能毫无心理压力地在远处
Lets just say that I find it much more comfortable...
- 欣赏着你的表演 - 心理舒适 那是进步的绊脚石
- admiring your show from afar. - Comfort, the enemy of progress.
你要知道 哪怕我只是辅助你
Do you understand that just associating with you
我也会丢掉遗产继承权的
could cost me my inheritance.
你丢掉的可不止这个
I thought it'd cost you more than that.
你这就是孤注一掷
You would be risking everything.
但是从另一个角度来看的话呢
But, on the other hand, well,
你可以认为你得到了自由
you just might find yourself a free man.
此时此地
Right here, right now I put the offer out.
我像你发出邀请
I don't want to chase you down I know you see it.
我不想死缠烂打 我相信你也看到光明的前景
You run with me. And I can cut you free.
你我并肩 向自由前行
Out of the drudgery and walls you keep in.
不受束缚 摆脱监禁
So trade that typical for something colorful.
忘掉固有 迎向缤纷未来的降临
And if it's crazy, live a little crazy.
活得疯狂一点又如何
You can play it sensible, a king of conventional.
你可以循规蹈矩
Or you can risk it all and see.
也可以放飞自我 亲自去见证
Don't you wanna get away from
你难道不想逃离这墨守成规的人生
same old part you gotta play.
我有你所需
'Cause I got what you need.
来吧 跟我去兜风
So come with me and take the ride.
体验所有的不同
It'll take you to the other side.
你可以一成不变 也可以想我看齐
'Cause you can do like you do Or you can do like me.
你可以选择牢笼 也可摆脱掌控
Stay in the cage, or you'll finally take the key.
哦 你终得悠然翱翔于天空
Oh, damn! Suddenly you're free to fly.
体验所有的不同
It'll take you to the other side.
我的朋友 你想和我并肩
Okay, my friend, you want to cut me in.
可我只能给你泼冷水 因为这些都不会发生
Well I hate to tell you, but it just won't happen.
心领了 但是不可能
So thanks, but no. I think I'm good to go.
我想我该离开了 你所说的束缚 我还享受其中
'Cause I quite enjoy the life you say I'm trapped in.
我很钦佩 你和你的演出
Now I admire you, and that whole show you do.
你的眼光很准 直觉很灵
You're onto something, really it's something.
但我们属于不同的世界 可谓泾渭分明
But I live among the swells, and we don't pick up peanut shells.
我只能劝你别纠缠不清
I'll have to leave that up to you.
你还不懂吗
Don't you know that I'm okay with
我无所谓我现在做的事情
this uptown part I get to play.
我已拥有一切 不会同你前行
'Cause I got what I need and I don't want to take the ride
我不想体验你所谓的不同
I don't need to see the other side.
你可以继续奋斗 我会回到我的生活
So go and do like you do. I'm good to do like me.
我不须摆脱什么 因为没有束缚我的牢笼
Ain't in a cage, so I don't need to take the key.
哦 难道你看不出我过得悠闲自在？
Oh, damn! Can't you see I'm doing fine?
我不想体验你所谓的不同
I don't need to see the other side.
这就是你想要的日子？
Now is this really how you like to spend your days?
酗酒纵情 苦乐不知
Whiskey and misery, and parties and plays.
如果我跟你混 会成为人们茶余饭后的谈资
If I were mixed up with you, I'd be the talk of the town.
卑微不堪 自欺欺人的傻子
Disgraced and disowned, another one of the clowns.
但你的人生会多一些欢笑 多一些真实
But you would finally live a little, finally laugh a little.
我可以给你梦想的自由
Just let me give you the freedom to dream and it'll wake you up
睁开双眼 治愈心灵的伤痛
and cure your aching.
摆脱桎梏 摧毁樊笼
Take your walls and start 'em breaking.
我的这份提议 应值得认同
Now that's a deal that seems worth taking.
但我会让你自己做决定
But I guess I'll leave that up to you.
很有吸引力 但我会付出很大的代价
Well it's intriguing, but to go would cost me greatly.
让我协助你的演出 你会出什么样的价码
So what percentage of the show would I be taking?
好吧 你想分一杯羹是吧
Fair enough, you'd want a piece of all the action.
给你7%收益 就这么定啦
I'd give you seven, we could shake and make it happen.
我又不是3岁小孩子 我要18%
I wasn't born this morning, eighteen would be just fine.
我看你还不如去抢呢
Why not just go ahead and ask for nickels on the dime?
-  15% -  我给你8%
- 15. - I'm doing eight.
-  12% -  9%
- 12. - 9吧
10%
先生 很荣幸成为你的合作伙伴
Sir, it looks like you have yourself a junior partner.
在我看 你就是个高薪低劳的学徒
What I have is an overcompensated apprentice.
你难道不想逃离旧生活
Don't you wanna get away to a
体验人生新角色
whole new part you're gonna play.
我有你所需 跟我去兜风
'Cause I got what you need, so come with me and take the ride.
体验所有的不同
to the other side.
你可以向我学习 你可以想我看齐
So if you do like I do So if you do like me.
忘掉樊笼 我们知道如何主宰这里
Forget the cage, 'cause we know how to make the key.
哦 眨眼间我们已可自由翱翔天空
Oh, damn! Suddenly we're free to fly.
我们会体验所有的不同
We're going to the other side.
-  你可以向我学习 -  体验所有的不同
So if you do like I do. To the other side.
-  你可以想我看齐 -  我们会体验所有的不同
So if you do like me.
只要我们愿意 就会体验所有的不同
'Cause if we do
我们会体验所有的不同
we're going to the other side.
她是谁？
Who is that?
嘿 嘿 飞一半怎么就回来 去前台完成表演
Hey. No one is buying hats back here. Get out front, go.
来 W·D·惠勒  安·惠勒  我给你们介绍一下 这是我新雇来的 他叫菲利普·卡莱尔
WD, Anne, I want to introduce my newest hire, Mr Philip Carlyle.
- 很荣幸见到你 - 我也是
- It's a pleasure to meet you. - Yeah, pleasure.
你有什么绝活？ 卡莱尔先生
And what is your act, Mr. Carlyle?
我没有绝活
I don't have an act.
这里每个人都有绝活的
Everyone has got an act.
- 巴纳姆先生 - 怎么了
- Mr. Barnum. - Yeah?
你最好过来看一下
You better come see this.
菲利普 过来啊
Philip, keep up.
- 真糟糕啊 - 一直都是这样啊
- A bit of nasty element. - They're always is, isn't it?
世间任何群体的存在都会有其他群体抵触
Nothing draws a crowd crying like a crowd.
滚回家怪物们
Go home you freaks.
城市的污点
"Shame of the city".
抗议者们认为巴纳姆先生的名誉
"The protests amend Mr. Barnum's reputation..."
是建立在经营无礼和下流的基础上的
"as a previewer of the offensive and indecent."
无礼和下流 本内特先生 我都脸红了
"Offensive and indecent." Mr. Bennett, I'm blushing.
我才脸红了呢
No, I'm blushing.
谁在乎本内特说什么
What do you care what Bennett thinks?
- 他是个混蛋 - 势利小人一个
- He's a prick. - And a snob.
是啊 全纽约的势力眼们都看到他的评语了
Yeah, all the snobs in the New York are reading me.
他很会迎合这帮人
Does their thinking for them.
这不过是他一家之言
What ever happened to the thriving of controversy?
这话倒是没错
Yeah, well... Look, hey..
这事你有什么看法？ - 菲利普
- Do you have any thoughts on this? - Philip.
- 事实上 我确实有 - 海伦 别闹了
- As a matter of fact, I do. - Helen, come on.
宫务大臣受女王旨意
"The master of the Household, has it in the command of the Queen...
邀请P·T·巴纳姆先生 及其剧场团队成员参加
To invite Mr. Phineas T Barnum and his theatrical
白金汉宫的招待会
troop to a reception at Buckingham Palace."
- 真是维多利亚女王的邀请？ - 我动了点私人关系
- The Queen Victoria? Is this real? - I had to pull a few strings.
想要社会接纳你们
If you want society to accept you,
最好从最高端人群下手
you may as well start at the very very top.
我们都在受邀之列吗？
Are we all invited?
我想我只能跟女王说这些人要么全去
I guess I'll just have to tell the queen either all of us go
要么谁也不会去
or none of us will.
英国女王 这真是再好不过了
The Queen of England. Can't get much better than that.
- 为什么我们不穿燕尾服 - 因为我们是来表演的
- Why aren't we in tails? - We are the entertainment.
你不是只想穿戏服的吗？
I don't see you in a costume.
女王陛下  来自美国的P·T·巴纳姆
Your Majesty, Mr Phineas T Barnum and his...
和他的...奇葩伙伴
Oddities from America.
那是真的么
Is that real?
女王陛下 请允许我向您介绍 巴纳姆先生
Your Majesty, may I present Mr Barnum.
见到您是我的荣幸 巴纳姆先生
The honor is mine, Mr. Barnum.
我的美国朋友跟我说了很多
And I've heard all about your little colonel
关于你那个小上校的事情
from my friends in America.
是将军 女王陛下
General, ma'am.
他比我想得还玲珑一些
You are even smaller than I imagined.
您也不算是大个子啊 亲爱的女王
Well, you are not exactly reaching the top self yourself sweetheart.
一切还算顺利
Ah, that went well.
- 女王陛下 - 菲利普
- Your Majesty. - Philip.
珍妮·琳德女士
Miss Jenny Lind.
真是光彩照人
She is really luminous.
- 她是谁？ - 歌剧演唱家
- Who is that? - The opera singer.
演唱家？
Singer, huh?
她是享誉全欧洲的表演家
She is the most famous performer in all of Europe.
她在斯卡拉歌剧院（米兰著名歌剧院）表演过很多次
She has sold out La Scala a dozen times.
更不用提她演唱过的法国歌剧了
Not to mention the French Opera.
真是太漂亮了
Striking.
- 你这是干什么？ - 跟着你啊
- What are you doing? - Following you...
- 这样你就能把我介绍给林德女士了
so you can introduce me to Miss Lind.
- 介绍你？ - 对啊
- Introduce you? - Yeah.
我都不认识她
I don't know her.
大家都认识她 你自己都这么说了
Everybody knows her. You just said so yourself.
- 对啊 你不能就这么直接过去..
Yeah, exactly. You don't just walk up to someone right now.
有什么不行的 我是人 她也是
Why not? We are presentable. She is a person.
林德女士 我叫菲利普·卡莱尔
Miss Lind. My name is Phillip Carlyle.
我身边这位杰出的男士是...
And this extraordinary gentleman next to me...
菲尼亚斯·泰勒·巴纳姆 见到您 我荣幸之至
Phineas Taylor Barnum. The pleasure is mine.
是啊 你是那个美国人 我想我可能听说过你
Of course, you are the American. I believe I might have heard of you.
如果你在这么远都听过在下微名
Oh well, If you've heard of me all the way over here,
这说明我干的还不错
I must have been doing something right.
也有人说是非常烂
That, or something very wrong.
舆论界观点不一
In the world of publicity there is hardly any difference.
巴纳姆先生 媒体都说你是个骗子呢
I believe those are the words of a scoundrel, Mr Barnum.
马戏团老板 林德女士 我是大西洋对岸最好的马戏团老板
A showman, Miss Lind, just a showman. The best on my side of the Atlantic.
- 我想你只是在自夸 - 我是在夸自己 但我是什么样的人不用我自己说
- If you just say so yourself. - I do, but I don't have to.
不是 他确实是顶尖之一呢
Oh, no, no. He is one of the best.
非常感谢 林德女士 我就直说了吧
That's very kind of you. Miss Lind, let me get to the point.
我想带您去纽约 如果你同意的话
I would like to bring you to New York. And if you agree...
我会让你不只是享誉全欧洲的女歌唱家 更是享誉全世界的女歌唱家
I will make you the most famous singer not in Europe but in the entire world.
你听过我唱歌吗?
And have you heard me sing?
- 没 没有 我没听过  - 当然听过
- Absolutely. - No, I haven't.
但是 在我看来 你声名远扬
But like mine, your reputation precedes you...
比起自己的品位我更相信你的名气
and well, I trust your reputation more than my own taste, so...
可我从来没去过美国
I have never been to America.
你会在一个宏伟的戏院演出
You will sing in the grandest theater...
在这个世界上最伟大的城市 有优秀的交响乐团伴奏
with the finest orchestra in the greatest city on earth.
宣传语就写"珍妮·林德: 只在今晚" "或者连演两晚"
"Jenny Lind". "One night only." Or maybe two.
收入的两成给你 对你来说应该不少
And at 20% at the gate, it will be a queen's ransom for your..
我的收入大多捐给了孤儿和寡妇
I gave most of my earnings to charity, Mr Barnum...
巴纳姆先生
to orphans and widows.
"夜莺般的声音 天使的心肠"
"Voice of a nightingale, Heart of an Angel."
好主意 报纸们会喜欢这个故事
That's brilliant. I mean the press will go crazy with that story.
这不只是说说而已
That's not a story.
我能问你个问题吗 巴纳姆先生?
May I ask you something, Mr. Barnum?
随便问
Anything.
为什么选我？
Why me?
人们来看我的表演 是为了看我们演出来的东西
People come to my show for the pleasure of being hoodwinked.
哪怕只有一次 我想让他们看看真实的东西
Just once, I would love to give them something real.
林德小姐
Miss Lind.
每个人都来了 你看看 甚至温思罗普家的人都来了
Everyone is here. Look at this. Even the Winthrops.
- 你高兴吗？ - 当然 如果一切顺利的话
- Are you happy? - I will be, if this works.
我的天 希望她能一唱惊人
Oh, God, I hope she can sing.
- 怎么花这么长时间  - 他们还在就座
- What's taking her so long? - They are still taking their seats.
说到这个 汤姆和莱蒂 还有其他人刚到
Speaking of which. Tom and Lettie, the others, they just arrived.
- 什么?  - 我应该把他们带到哪去 你的包厢
- What? - Where should I put them? Your box?
- 不不 太显眼了 - 显眼?
- That box? No, that's pretty visible. - Visible?
让他们去站座吧 那边音效其实更好
The acoustics are actually better in the standing room.
那才是他们应该去的地方
That's where they should be.
- 林德小姐准备好了  - 好的 谢谢
- Miss Lind is ready now. - OK. Thank you. Thank God.
这个地方很棒
This is so beautiful.
- 很棒是不是?  - 是的
- Isn't that beautiful? - Yes.
我喜欢这里
I love it.
女士和先生们 感谢你们的耐心
Ladies and gentlemen, thank you for your patience.
最近我有幸能听到自己此前从未听过的美妙声音
I recently had the privilege of hearing the most divine voice...
- 我听过 - 突然他就成音乐鉴赏家了
- I've ever heard. - Suddenly he's a connoisseur.
我知道这听起来像一个骗局
Now, I know that sounds like Barnum humbug...
但我现在准备了一百瓶上好香槟庆功
but I have a 100 bottles of good champagne on ice that says
我不想说这是另一个目光短浅的决定
that this is not just another sideshow novelty.
让我向大家介绍瑞典夜莺
May I present, the Swedish Nightingale...
珍妮·林德小姐!
Miss Jenny Lind.
我尽力摒住呼吸
I'm trying to hold to my breath
让它定格
let it stay that way.
不让此刻幻然消逝
Can't let this moment end.
你和我共同建筑的梦
You set off a dream with me.
已然震撼人心
Getting louder now.
你能听到此梦回响吗?
Can you hear it echoing?
握住我的手
Take my hand.
你会与我共享此刻的风景吗?
Will you share this with me?
因为没有你
'Cause darling without you.
即使聚光灯缤纷闪耀
All the shine of a thousand spotlights.
即使盗来满天的星辰
All the stars we steal from the night sky
仍有所缺憾
will never be enough
仍不能圆满
never be enough.
琼楼玉宇变得轻贱
Towers of gold are still too little.
纵然手握世界
These hands could hold the world
也不能知足
but it will never be enough
仍不能圆满
never be enough
于我而言
for me!
永远 永远
never, never,
永远 对我而言
never for me.
对我而言
never enough,
永不圆满
永远缺憾
never enough,
对我而言
for me, for me
for me.
即使聚光灯缤纷闪耀
All the shine of a thousand spotlights.
即使盗来满天的星辰
All the stars we steal from the night sky
仍有所缺憾
will never be enough
仍不能圆满
never be enough.
琼楼玉宇变得轻贱
Towers of gold are still too little.
纵然手握世界
These hands could hold the world
也不能知足
but it will never be enough
仍不能圆满
never be enough
对我而言
for me
永远 永远
never never
永远 对我而言
never for me
对我而言
for me
永远不够
never enough never, never
永远 永远
never enough for me
对我而言
for me, for me
for me.
真棒
Bravo.
真厉害
唱得太好了
Superb.
太棒了
Bravo.
Awesome.
珍妮 这是我的妻子夏瑞蒂和我的女儿们
Jenny, this is my wife Charity and our girls.
你好 我听了你们的好多故事
Of course, and I've heard so much about you.
你父亲告诉我你喜欢芭蕾
And your father tells me you are a fan of the ballet.
- 是的 我在学习芭蕾  - 是么?
- Yes, I'm studying ballet. - Oh, are you?
- 当然是的  - 当然她是在学的
- Of course I am. - Of course she is.
- 那你呢 海伦  - 你看起来像个公主
- And what about you, Helen? - You look like a princess, ma'am.
我必须得承认 巴纳姆 她真是无与伦比
I have to admit, Barnum, she is remarkable.
好到可以给最不开心的评论家带来快乐 是不是
Enough to bring joy to the most joyless critic, isn't she?
在一个行家手里
And in the hands of a real previewer of the art...
她能在这个国家有很大的成就
she could be something in this country.
真可惜她堕落到了你的手里
Shame she's fallen in with you.
你还是适合为小报工作 你所说的没人会信
You really are better on the page, Mr Banner. How does that is to believe.
巴纳姆先生 我希望能见见琳达小姐
Oh, Mr. Barnum? I would love to meet Miss Lind.
好的 琳达小姐  给我一分钟 我想
And you will meet miss Lind if you just give me a moment...
- 菲尼亚斯? - 嗯?
- Phineas. - Yes.
你做的很好
You've done well.
谢谢
Thank you.
请允许我把她介绍给你
Allow me to introduce you.
打扰一下 珍妮 让我向你介绍夏瑞蒂的父母
Excuse me, Jenny. I would like you to meet Charity's parents.
- 哈利特先生和夫人  - 很荣幸
- Mr and Mrs Hallett. - Ah, pleasure.
- 你好吗?  - 见到你很高兴
- How do you do? Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you.
- 妈妈  - 你好 宝贝女儿
- Mother. - Hello dear.
- 这些是 - 这些是你的外孙女们
- Are these... - Yes, yes, those are your granddaughters.
- 菲尼亚斯 不要在这  - 不要在这?
- Phineas, not here. - Not here?
你怕着我会在这些体面的朋友面前
You are afraid that I'm gonna embarrass your
让你的父母难堪吗?
parents in front of their fancy friends?
我真不觉得我有这样的能耐
I really don't think that I have that power.
一个像我这样的小人物
An insignificant man like me...
一定会有过平庸的日子
was clearly destined to lead an insignificant life.
就算有着这些成就 你也还只是个裁缝的儿子
All that fortune and still just a tailor's boy.
滚出去
Get out.
哦 菲尼亚斯!我记得我告诉过你
Well, Phineas...
免费的香槟是
I believe that I told you that free champagne
痛苦的良药
is a recipe for disaster.
夏瑞蒂
Charity.
请大家举杯
Now would everyone please raise their glasses?
感谢巴纳姆先生所向我们展现的一切
To Mr Barnum, who showed once and for all...
这位男士所能取得的成就 只有想不到 没有做不到的
that a man's station is limited only by his imagination.
- 敬巴纳姆  - 谢谢
- To Barnum. - Thank you.
敬巴纳姆先生
To Mr Barnum.
谢谢
Thank you.
当你生来就有财富和特权的时候 它们就会变得很难理解
It's hard to understand wealth and privileges when you're born into it.
有时候我觉得自己不属于这里
I sometimes don't feel like I belong here.
为什么?
You?
我是个私生子
I was born out of wedlock
这让我的家人蒙羞
and that brought shame upon my family.
生活总是要提醒我
And life always manages to remind me
我不配在这个世界有一席之地
that I don't deserve a place in this world.
这让给我留下了永远填不上的空洞
And that leaves a hole that no ovation can ever fill.
菲尼亚斯先生
Mr. Phineas.
- 那位女士真是太棒了  - 我知道
- Lord, that lady can sing. - I know.
她喜欢穿制服的男人吗
Thinks she likes a man in uniform?
我确定她喜欢的
I'm sure she does.
你们在这干什么?你们的演出还有一个小时就开始了
What are you doing here? You got a show in an hour, OK?
这个时间至少可以喝个三杯 让我们进去吧
That's enough time for us to have at least three drinks, right? Come on.
- 不不不 莱蒂! - 怎么了?
- No no. Lettie. - What?
里面已经人很满了 我不能让你们这样进去招摇
It's very crowder in here, okay? And I can't have you mingling.
对于个人来说 如果这么轻易把你们都暴露给大家
Who's gonna pay admission
谁还会付钱来看你们?
if you are out there for all the world to see.
- 好好演出! - 等等
- Have a great show. - Wait...
女士们和先生们 干杯
Ladies and gentlemen, a toast.
珍妮 美国人民还不知道你 但是他们会爱上你的
Jenny, America may not know it yet, but they are going to love you.
敬珍妮·林德
To Miss Lind.
早已习惯长夜漫漫
I am not a stranger to the dark.
众人劝我 销声匿迹
"Hide away," they say.
皆因我已声名狼藉
"'Cause we don't want your broken parts"
众人劝我远走高飞
I've learned to be ashamed of all my scars.
无人待我视如己出
"Run away," they say "No one will love you as you are."
但我未被击垮跌入尘埃
But I won't let them break me down to dust
我心有一片方寸地
I know that there's a place for us.
容下我们的光彩荣耀
For we are glorious.
锋言利刃袭来之时
When the sharpest words wanna cut me down.
我排山倒海溃退之
I'm gonna send a flood, gonna drown them out.
我勇敢过 我受伤过
I am brave, I am bruised I am who I'm meant to be
我注定与众不同
this is me. Look out 'cause here I come.
我将卷土重来
And I'm marching on to the beat I drum.
我将重整旗鼓
I'm not scared to be seen I make no apologies,
不惧言语不畏世俗
this is me.
勇往直前至死不屈
What are they doing here?
他们来这干什么?
Another round of bullets hits my skin.
枪林弹雨再临
Well, fire away.
我们火力全开不屈不挠
'Cause today, I won't let the shame sink in.
我们越过重重障碍
We are bursting through the barricades and reaching for the sun,
终将拨云见日 我们是勇士
we are warriors.
是的 那就是我们的未来
Yeah, that's what we've become.
但我未被击垮跌入尘埃
Won't let them break me down to dust.
- 我心有一片方寸地  - 滚回家去吧！
- I know that there's a place for us.   - Freaks, go home.
容下我们的光彩荣耀
For we are glorious.
锋言利刃袭来之时
When the sharpest words wanna cut me down.
我排山倒海溃退之
Gonna send a flood, gonna drown them out.
我勇敢过 我受伤过
I am brave, I am bruised
我注定如此
I am who I'm meant to be,
这就是我
this is me.
我将卷土重来
Look out 'cause here I come.
我将重整旗鼓
And I'm marching on to the beat I drum.
不惧言语不畏世俗
I'm not scared to be seen. I make no apologies.
这就是我
This is me
This is me.
汝之所向吾之所往
And I know that I deserve your love.
光芒万丈无人能挡
There's nothing I'm not worthy of.
锋言利刃袭来之时
When the sharpest words wanna cut me down.
我排山倒海溃退之
I'm gonna send a flood, gonna drown them out.
这是勇敢 这是受伤
This is brave, this is bruised.
我注定这样
This is who I'm meant to be,
这就是我
this is me.
我将卷土重来
Look out 'cause here I come.
我将重整旗鼓
And I'm marching on to the beat I drum.
不惧言语
Marching on, marching, marching on.
不畏世俗
I'm not scared to be seen. I make no apologies.
这就是我
This is me.
锋言利刃袭来之时
When the sharpest words wanna cut me down.
我排山倒海溃退之
I'm gonna send a flood, gonna drown them out
我排山倒海
I'm gonna send a flood,
这就是我
this is me.
你为什么不只在纽约表演?
Why can't you just put more shows in New York?
你为什么要去巡演?
Why do you need t tour the country?
为什么拿破仑要侵犯俄罗斯
Why did Napoleon march on Russia?
拿破仑被打败了
Napoleon was defeated.
他没有六十位音乐家的乐团
Napoleon didn't have a 60 piece orchestra.
六十位音乐家
A 60 piece orchestra.
找那种最便宜的 你自己把握
Just get the cheapest musicians you can, you watch that.
我们还得让他们上船啊
We still have to aboard them.
找那种夫妻二人都是音乐家的 可以睡一张床 奥马利可以想办法搞些钱
Get married ones. They can share a bunk. O'Malley, that's Caroline's piggy bank.
购置服装 在戏院里放烟花?
Costumes sets? Fireworks? Inside theaters?
- 这主意太棒了  - 不! 巴纳姆!
That's genius.
这些都是全国最有名的戏院
No. These are the most famous theaters in the country.
- 你要提前付出场费的 - 我借了些钱
- They make you buy their seats in advance. - Yeah, yeah. I took out a loan.
我们还要付钱给珍妮?
And we have to pay Jenny?
我其实借了好些钱
It was a large loan, okay?
我们在四十场之前赚不到一分钱
You're not gonna see a penny of profit until your 40th show.
确切说是在第四十一场才能赚到钱
41st actually.
你把一切都赌上了
You're risking everything you've built here.
有没有想过如果我成功了
How do you think I build it?
我们之后会赚得盆满钵满
We'll have plenty of profits to go around after this.
- 巴纳姆? - 怎么了?
- P. T? - What?
你的注意力太分散了
Your attention has been divided long enough.
我们的观众在减少 反对者日渐增加
Our gate is down, we have more protesters every day.
那就让观众们回来
You just need to get people to come back.
"如果你最近没到巴纳姆博物馆看看
"If you haven't been to Barnum museum lately...
那就最好到巴纳姆博物馆看看"
You have not been to the Barnum Museum."
观众们来是看你的
The come to see you.
看你的疯狂的想法 看你的新举动 你那不一般的做法
Your crazy ideas, your new acts, the unusual.
说到不一般 那么试试多微笑 那会不一般的
Then have you show them your smile. That would be unusual.
继续彩排 然后把话说清楚
Keep rehearsing. Just make it very clear that I expect
他们会给你应得的尊重
them to afford you all the deference you deserve...
不管怎么样他们都会对你非常友好
And that they should be nice to you anyway.
真是一个悲伤的场面
Ain't that a sight for sore eyes?
- 你们能不能至少打个招呼 - 或者说声再见
- He couldn't even say hello. - Or goodbye.
他要去巡演了 真不好意思 各位
He is going on tour. Sorry guys.
冷静一下 卡莱尔! 自己找个地方待着去吧
Pull yourself together, Carlyle. Don't you have somewhere to be?
我是安·惠勒
Anne Wheeler.
巴纳姆先生留了一张票给我
Mr. Barnum said he left a ticket for me.
不好意思
I'm sorry.
- 我觉得应该是一张 - 不 就是两张
- I believe this one supposed to be one. - No, there's meant to be two.
不知道告诉你了你会不会来
Wasn't sure you'd come if I asked.
五分钟后开场
Five minutes to curtains.
我一直想到戏院看看
I've always wanted to go to the theater.
菲利普 是你吗?
Phillip, is that you?
妈妈 爸爸
Mother. Father.
这位是安·惠勒
This is Anne Wheeler.
菲利普 你就没有一点羞耻心吗?
Phillip, have you no shame?
和巴纳姆一起做生意是一回事
To associate yourself with that Barnum business is one thing...
但是和一个下等人在一起?
but parading around with that elf.
安
Anne.
你怎么能这么对她说话
How dare you speak to her like that?
- 你忘了你的地位  - 我的地位?
- You forget your place, Phillip. - My place?
妈妈 如果这是我的地位 那我不想要
Mother, if this is my place, then I don't wanna be a part of it.
安
Anne.
他们是刻薄的人
They are small minded people.
- 为什么你要在乎这些事  - 这些不是小事
- Why do you care what they say? - It's not just them.
从来没有人像你父母那样对待我们
Never had somebody look at you the way your parents looked at me.
看看他们如何看待我们的
The way everyone would look at us.
你知道我对你的爱慕
You know I want you.
我并不想掩盖这一旦
It's not a secret I try to hide.
我知晓你对我的眷恋
I know you want me.
所以不要再说我们只是迫于无奈
So don't keep saying our hands are tied.
你宣称的一切都未尘埃落定
You claim it's not in the cards.
但命运却已经将你远远拖离
And fate is pulling you miles away.
我失去了触碰你的距离
And out of reach from me.
但你却已深藏在我的心里 你若决意谁又能阻挠
But you're here in my heart. So who can stop me if I decide
我将你看做是我命运的追寻
that you are my destiny?
若我们重摹写繁星的轨迹
What if we rewrite the stars?
把你与我写成命中注定
Say you were made to be mine.
我们将永不分离
Nothing could keep us apart.
我走上的道路都会通向你
You'd be the one I was meant to find.
一切都取决于你我
It's up to you, and it's up to me.
没人可以左右我们的未来
No one can say what we get to be.
如我们重摹繁星轨迹
So why don't we rewrite the stars?
或许我们今晚便可以把世界握在手心
Maybe the world could be ours, tonight.
你或许觉得你更容易接近
You think it's easy?
你或许觉得我不想奔向你
You think I don't want to run to you.
可连绵的群山
But there are mountains.
和一道道关卡让我们寸步难行
And there are doors that we can't walk through.
我明白你的迷惑不解
I know you're wondering why.
我们本来可以融为一体
Because we're able to be
只有你和我 在这有限的空间之中
Just you and me within these walls.
可当我们面对世界的风险 你将会从梦中醒来
But when we go outside, you're gonna wake up and see that
看到我们的前路一切无望
that it was hopeless after all.
没人可以把繁星天迹重写
No one can rewrite the stars.
你又怎么说你将属于我
How can you say you'll be mine?
这世间的一切都在阻挠着我们
Everything keeps us apart.
我并不是你生命里的唯一
And I'm not the one you were meant to find.
你无计可施 我也无力改变
It's not up to you, it's not up to me.
当每个人都告诉我们前路暗淡
When everyone tells us what we can be.
我们何以重摹繁星?
How can we rewrite the stars?
妄言今夜我们会拥有世界
Say that the world can be ours, tonight.
我只想与你遨游天际
All I want is to fly with you.
只想伴你一同坠落
All I want is to fall with you.
所以放心把你托付与我
So just give me all of you.
- 这毫无可能  - 这并非毫无可能
It feels impossible It's not impossible.
- 真的可能?  - 是要你我相信
Is it impossible? See that it's possible.
我们怎样重摹繁星?
How do we rewrite the stars?
来让你成我的命中注定
Say you were made to be mine?
再无什么可以让我分离
Nothing can keep us apart.
因为你就是我走向的唯一
Cause you are the one I was meant to find.
一切都在你 也在我的手中掌握
It's up to you, and it's up to me.
没人可以左右我们的未来
No one can say what we get to be.
那就让我们重摹繁星轨迹
And why don't we rewrite the stars?
让这世界尽归我们掌握
Changing the world to be ours.
你知道我对你的爱慕
You know I want you.
这并不是需要隐藏的秘密
It's not a secret I try to hide.
但是我却无法拥有你
But I can't have you.
我们注定要分离
We're bound to break and my hands are tied.
先是把房子买在和我父母同一条街
First it was buying a house on the same street as my parents.
觐见英国女王
Then meeting the queen.
把珍妮·林德带到美国来 然后是和我父亲那晚的事
Then bringing Jenny Lind, and my father the other night.
这些都不能让你知足么
When will it ever be enough for you?
我做这些都是为了卡洛琳和海伦
I am doing this for Caroline and Helen.
- 看看你周围 她们什么都有
Look around you. They have everything.
-  你不明白 - 我懂
- You don't understand. - I do.
不 你根本不明白!
No. You don't understand!
你怎么可能明白?
How could you?
他们都瞧不起我父亲
My father was treated like dirt.
也瞧不起我
I was treated like dirt.
但我的孩子绝对不会受到这种待遇
My children will not be.
你不需要让所有人喜欢你
You don't need everyone to love you, Phin.
那么几个人喜欢你就够了
Just a few good people.
我知道这道理
I know that.
- 谢谢 - 先生请上车
- Thank you. - Sir.
不要走
No. Daddy.
爸爸！
Daddy.
爸爸
Daddy, no. Wait.
- 爸爸 - 驾
- Daddy. - Go.
等等 不！
Wait, Daddy.
一些人想要 一个简简单单 按部就班的人生
Some people long for a life that is simple and planned.
被束缚也是心甘
Tied with a ribbon.
一些人不愿远航
Some people won't sail the sea
因为陆地安全得多
'cause they're safer on land.
他们屈服于自己的命运
To follow what's written.
但是我愿与你同行
But I'd follow you
探索无穷的未知
to the great unknown.
奔向那以
Off to a world
我们为名的世界
we call our own.
巅峰低谷 起起伏伏
Mountains and valleys, and all that will come in between
无边无际的沙漠与海洋
desert and ocean
你我卷入并陶醉在梦中
you pull me in
永不停歇
and together we're lost in a dream.
我毫无保留
Always in motion so I risk it all
只为和你在一起
just to be with you.
毫无保留
And I risk it all
为了我们选择的人生
for this life we choose.
紧握我的双手 向我保证 永不松开
Hand in my hand and you promised to never let go.
我们像走在钢丝上
We're walking the tightrope.
悬在高高的天空中
High in the sky.
俯瞰着世界
We can see the whole world down below.
我们像走在钢丝上
We're walking the tightrope.
充满了未知与可能
Never sure,
如果我坠下 你会不会将我紧紧抱住?
will you catch me if I should fall?
这是个冒险 其间美景非凡
Well, it's all an adventure that comes with a breathtaking view.
和你一起 走在钢丝上
Walking the tightrope
和你一起
with you
一起
with you.
“仿佛这是我们第一次
"It is as though we've learned for the first time..."
领会什么是真正的歌唱
what singing really is.
林德小姐值得整个国家最高的尊敬 和最热烈的喝彩
Miss Lind deserves our nation's highest esteem and lavish ovations.
- 嗯 我… - 全世界就在我们脚下
- I mean... - The world at our feet.
现在 巴纳姆先生
Well, Mr. Barnum.
我们
This...
来为
is...
梦想成真举杯
to making dreams come true.
谢谢你 珍妮
Thank you, Jenny.
演出剩下不多了
It's two hours to curtains.
我给了你所有 不是么?
I've given you the world, haven't I?
我想我该走了
I, I should go.
我对你没有好处 我很抱歉 珍妮
I have become a distraction. I'm sorry, Jenny.
- 不 你不需要我进行巡演 - 什么 你要离开?
- You should finish your tour without me. - What? You're leaving?
- 嗯 行程已经安排妥当了 - 就这样?
- The itinerary is well in hand. - So that's it.
- 你什么意思?
What do you mean?
我只是你达到目的的另一个棋子
I'm just another your acts.
- 我不做了 - 珍妮 珍妮
- Jenny. - I'm done.
珍妮 不要这样
Jenny, Jenny, please.
你必须要完成巡演
You have to finish the tour.
- 必须? - 否则这会毁了我的
- Must I? - It will ruin me.
当你对其他人不闻不问 巴纳姆先生
When you're careless with other people Mr Barnum...
你毁了你自己
you bring ruin upon yourself.
- 我赔上了我的所有 - 我也同样
- I have risked everything. - Well, so did I.
看来我们都亏了
And seems we've both lost.
夜空中你我摘下的星星
All the stars we steal
永远不足够
from the night sky.
他们永远不足够
Will never be enough
永远不足够
never be enough.
成堆的金钱仍然太少
Towers of gold are still too little.
这双手能拥有全世界
These hands could hold the world
但是却不能满足你的心
but it will never be enough
永远不能
never be enough.
谢谢
Thank you.
那是什么?
What was that?
是再见
That was goodbye.
谢谢你们的到场
Thank you very much for coming.
- 请分享给你们的朋友和家人 - 多么精彩的演出啊
- Say your fancy neighbors. - What a beautiful show.
谁享受这场盛宴? 你? 还是你?
Who enjoyed yourselves? You?
请告诉所有人这马戏团有多精彩
Tell everyone how much fun you
每晚都有新花样
had at the circus. New acts every night.
领班!
Hey, ringmaster.
先生们 我想请求你们离开
Gentlemen, I am gonna have to ask you to leave.
这是我们的小镇 伙计
This is our town, son.
该走的是你们 你
We think you should leave, you and your freaks.
和你的那些怪物朋友们
And yours spooks.
先生
Sir.
我最后说一遍 请你离开
I will only ask once more.
否则你能拿我怎样?
Then what, boy?
揍他们
Attack.
爸爸 爸爸
Daddy.
姑娘们 孩子 孩子
- Daddy. Daddy! - Girls.
他们竟然长了那么多了
You have grown so much.
“你怎么回来早了些?” - 我想你们了
What made you decide to come back early?
我想你
I missed you.
-  听起来像是你的托词  - 着火了!
- That sounds lawful. - Fire.
让开 着火了 快点! 是马戏团那边的
- Out of the way. Fire! - Hurry, it's coming from the circus.
- 着火了! - 跟我来 来 快点
Girls, stay with me. Come, quickly.
大家听好了 跟紧点
Everyone! Stay close.
菲利普 菲利普 菲利普 大家都出来了么?
Phillip, is everyone out?
大家还好么? 动物们呢?
Is everyone okay? The animals?
我们把他们放走了 别无选择
We set them free. What else could we do?
- W·D 安在哪? - 她在哪? 她在哪?
- WD, where is Anne? - Where is Anne?
不! 菲利普 不!
No, Phillip.
菲利普! 不 你不能进去
No. Stop. You can not go inside.
继续抽水
Keep pumping.
- W·D! - 在这儿 他在这儿
- WD. - There she is.
- 菲利普 菲利普 - 爸爸
- Phillip. - Daddy.
爸!
- No dad. - Daddy.
不
No.
请退后
Stay back, please.
爸
Daddy.
担架快来!
Stretcher, stretcher.
他吸入太多的烟 但他还活着 快走
He has taken a lot of smoke. He's still breathing.
来把他抬上担架!
Let's get him on.
抬起来
Up.
若我们重摹繁星轨迹
What if we rewrite the stars?
把你我写成命中注定
Say you were meant to be mine?
永不分离
Nothing can keep us apart
我注定要与你相逢
you are the one I was meant to find.
我们走
Here we go.
快 就在前面
Come on, straight ahead.
如果你是来幸灾乐祸的 那请便吧 我不会回嘴的
If you had come to gloat I wouldn't.
他们抓住了放火的那些人
They caught the thugs who started the fire.
我想你会感兴趣
I thought you'd like to know.
我从没有喜欢过你的演出
I never liked your show.
但是我一直认为人们的确是喜欢看的
But I always thought the people did.
现在也是如此
They do.
我并不会它称之为艺术
Mind you, I wouldn't call it art.
当然不
Of course not.
但是
But...
把各种各样的人拉上舞台
Putting folks of all kinds on stage.
各种肤色 体型 身高的人 一视同仁…
All colors, shapes, sizes. Presenting them as equals.
其他的评论家或许会称这为
Another critic might have even called it
“人性的礼赞”
'a celebration of humanity'.
我会中意这说法的
I would have liked that.
我期望你能重建马戏团
Well, I hope you'll rebuild.
通过珍妮的巡演 我们能有些盈余
Thank god for Jenny's tour. We can borrow off the profits.
能挺过去的
We'll be fine.
你不知道那回事儿么?
You don't know?
珍妮·林德退出
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
丑闻缠身的巴纳姆
Charity?
夏瑞蒂 天哪 夏瑞蒂
Oh God, Charity.
- 我… - 我不想跟你说话
- I am... - I don't wanna talk to you.
- 什么事都没有发生 - 是么
- Nothing happened. - Ouch, nothing happened.
每张报纸都在刊登这个事情
It's on the cover of every paper in New York.
这是她谋划的 我并不爱她
Because she orchestrated the photo. I am not in love with her.
当然不
Of course you're not.
不是为了她 不是我或任何其他人
Not with her, not with me, not with anyone.
是为了你自己和你的演出
Just you and your show.
你要干什么?
What are you doing?
我要回家
I'm going home.
这才是你家
This is your home.
银行
The bank..
银行把我们赶出去了
They are evicting us.
你为什么不跟我商量?
Why didn't you ask me before?
我会同意的
I would have said yes.
我从不怕什么风险 只要我们能一同面对
I never minded the risk, but we always did it together.
我估摸你会来这儿的 自怨自哀
Figured you'd end up here. Feeling sorry for yourself?
如果他们来讨要酬劳 我一分钱都没了
Folks if you have come to get paid, the money's gone. All of it.
- 付不起 - 他妈的别说了 巴纳姆
- Nothing left to give... - Shut up, Barnum.
你根本不理解我们
You just don't get it.
就连我们的母亲都视我们为耻辱
Our own mothers were ashamed of us.
她们试图掩盖我们的存在
Hid us our whole lives.
是你把我们救出阴霾的
Then you pull us out of the shadows.
但现在就连你也要放弃我们
And now you are giving upon us too.
也许你是个骗子
Maybe you are fraud.
也许你做这些只是为了金钱
Maybe it was just about making a buck.
但你给我们了一个真正的家
But you gave us a real family.
这个马戏团…
And the circus...
就是我们的家
That was our home.
我们要重建我们的家
We want our home back.
我看到太阳散失光芒
I saw the sun begin to dim.
我感到冬日彻骨的寒风
And felt that winter wind blow cold.
一个人终于找到他的归属
A man learns who is there for him.
当闪烁的光亮暗淡 当坚实的后盾倒塌
When the glitter fades and the walls won't hold.
因为从那时起留下的只有碎石瓦砾
'Cause from then, rubble
留下的
one remains.
只有我真正拥有的
Can only be once true.
如果丧失所有
If all was lost.
能够得到更多
There's more I gained.
那一定是因为
Cause it led me back
你回到了我的身边
to you.
我曾与皇室共饮香槟
I drank champagne with kings and queens
政客颂扬我的大名
the politicians praised my name.
然而那都是别人的梦
But those are someone else's dreams.
那是对我的诱惑和考验
The pitfalls of the man I became.
年复一年 我渴望他们的赞扬
For years and years I chased their cheers.
疯狂地渴求更多
The crazy speed of always needing more.
但当我停下脚步 看到了你们
But when I stop and see you here
我回想起了我的初心
I remember who all this was for
从此刻起
and from now on.
这双眼睛不会被光亮所蒙蔽
These eyes will not be blinded by the lights.
此刻起
From now on.
我不再等待下一个黎明
What's waited till tomorrow starts tonight
今夜启程
it starts tonight.
让我的许诺从这一刻生效
And let this promise in me start.
像我心中响起的圣歌般坚贞
Like an anthem in my heart
从这刻起
from now on
from now on.
我们回家
And we will come back home
我们踏上回家的路
home again.
重拾家的感觉
And we will come back home
我们回家
home again.
回家
And we will come back home
home again.
回家
From now on we will come back home.
从这刻起
And we will come back home
我们重返家园
home again.
回家
And we will come back home.
And we will come back home
回家
home again.
And we will come back home.
回家
And we will come back home
home again.
回家
And we will come back home from now on
and we will come home again from now on
回家
home again
从这刻起
from now on.
这双眼睛不会再被光亮蒙蔽
These eyes will not be blinded by the lights!
从这刻起
From now on!
我不再等待下一个黎明
What's waited till tomorrow starts tonight!
今夜启程
It starts tonight.
让承诺现在生效
Let this promise in me start.
像我心中的圣歌一样坚贞
Like an anthem in my heart
从这刻起
from now on
- 从这刻起 - 我们回家
from now on and we will come home again.
我们踏上回家的路
And we will come back home
重拾家的感觉
home again.
我们回家
And we will come back home
回家
home again.
你在这
You are here.
从这一刻起
From now on
from now on
回家
home again
从这一刻起
from now on
回家
home again
从这一刻起
from now on
回家
home again.
卡洛琳! 他来了
- Caroline. - He's here.
我想见我的妻子
I would like to see my wife.
她不在
She's not here.
她在海边!
She's at the beach.
我给你和我们的家带来了苦痛
I have brought hardships on you and our family.
你叮嘱过我
You warned me...
然而我没有听取
and I wouldn't listen.
我只是
I just wanted...
我渴望成为更棒的人
I wanted to be more than I was.
我只想要那个曾同我坠入爱河的男人 除此别无他求
I never wanted anything but the man I fell in love with.
让承诺就此兑现
Let this promise in me start.
如同圣歌般坚贞
Like an anthem in my heart
不管它有多么琐碎
however big
多么微不足道
however small
从这一刻起
from now on.
From now on.
- 银行拒绝了? - 嗯 不止一次地坚定地回绝了
- The bank said no? - Emphatically. And repeatedly.
我觉得全国没有一家银行
I don't think there is a bank left in this country...
愿意借给我们钱了
I can fool into loaning me more money, so...
很抱歉让你们失望了
I'm really sorry to disappoint you all.
别担心 我们都习惯了
Don't worry, Barnum. We've gotten used to it by now.
你知道么 巴纳姆…
You know, Barnum...
我遇见你的时候
when I first met you...
我可以继承丰厚的家产
I had an inheritance, claim...
出入各种豪华派对
and an invitation to every party in town.
而现在 多亏了你 那些都没了
And now thanks to you. All that's gone.
留下的只有友谊和爱
All that's left is this friendship, love
还有我热爱的工作
and work that I adore.
你让我的生活变得愉悦
You brought joy into my life.
我们每个人都是如此
- Into all our lives. - Yeah.
如果愉悦能用来抵押贷款就好了
I need a bank who takes joy as collateral.
他们大概不会
They may not...
不过我会同意
But I will.
演出获利的10%都是我的
I own 10% of the show.
考虑到我和你的情况
Knowing who I was working for...
我以前每周上班 拿走我的那部分前
I had the good sense to take my cut weekly.
菲利普 我不能让你在我身上冒险…
Phillip, I can't let you gamble it on me...
当然可以的
Sure you can.
别跟我讲那些大道理了
Don't turn sensible on us now.
合伙人
Partners.
五五分
Fifty fifty.
合伙人
Partners.
唯一的问题是…
The only this is...
我们怎么能把楼再盖起来
I don't know how we're gonna afford a building.
嗯
Right.
我们并不需要盖楼
We don't need a building.
在曼哈顿投资不动产挺糟糕的
Real estate in Manhattan is a terrible investment.
购置地产不划算
I can get a land down by the docks for almost nothing.
我们只需要一个帐篷
All we need is a tent.
这就是最佳表演
This is the most beautiful show. - Come on.
我们克服了如此的艰辛
Colossal we calm these renegades in the rain
我们会找回那渐失的荣耀
where the lost get found in the crown of the circus cage.
别抗拒 它为你而生 何不为它而活
Don't fight it, it's coming for you, running at ya.
就是现在 别去顾虑未来如何
It's only this moment, don't care what comes after.
哪怕外界一片黑暗
It's blinding outside and I think that you know.
放飞自我 那是你内心深处的呼唤
Just surrender 'cause you're calling and you wanna go.
那里没有异样的眼光
Where it's covered in all the colored lights.
那里都是为自我而战的人
Where the runaways are running the night.
一切皆有可能 你沉醉其中了吗
Impossible comes true, intoxicating you.
这就是最佳表演
Oh, this is the greatest show.
调动全身的激情 传奇永不落幕
We light it up, we won't come down.
精彩将持续上演
And the sun can't stop us now.
它真的实现了 你感受到了吗
Watching it come true, it's taking over you.
这就是最佳表演
Oh, this is the greatest show.
这有你向往的一切
It's everything you ever want.
这有你需要的所有
It's everything you ever need.
现在它近在咫尺
And it's here right in front of you.
这就是你的归宿
This is where you wanna be.
这有你向往的一切
It's everything you ever want.
这有你需要的所有
It's everything you ever need.
现在它近在咫尺
And it's here right in front of you.
这就是你的归宿
This is where you wanna be.
那里没有异样的眼光
When it's covered in all the colored lights.
那里都是为自我而战的人
Where the runaways are running the night.
这是给你的
Impossible comes true, - This is for you.
这就是最佳表演
it's taking over you Oh, this is the greatest show.
- 你要去哪儿? 看我的女孩儿长大
- What are you going to do? - Watching my girls grow up.
精彩将持续上演
The show must go on - We won't come down.
无可阻挡
And the sun can't stop us now.
它真的实现了 你感受到了吗
Watching it come true, it's taking over you.
这就是最佳表演
This is the greatest show.
那里没有异样的眼光
When it's covered in all the colored lights.
那里都是为自己而战的人
Where the runaways are running the night.
一切皆有可能 你感受到了吗
Impossible comes true, it's taking over you.
这就是最佳表演
Oh, this is the greatest show
调动全身的激情 传奇永不落幕
we won't come down.
无可阻挡
And the walls can't stop us now.
它真的实现了 你感受到了吗
I'm watching it come true, it's taking over you.
这就是最佳表演
Oh, this is the greatest show.
梦想近在咫尺
'Cause everything you want is right in front of you.
一切皆有可能
And you see the impossible is coming true.
无可阻挡
And the walls can't stop us now, yeah.
这就是最佳表演
This is the greatest show.
This is the greatest show!
爸爸!
Daddy.
嗨 姑娘们!
Hey, girls.
这就是最佳表演
Hey. Out of the way.
This is the greatest show.
这就是最佳表演
这有你向往的一切
It's everything you ever want.
It's everything you ever need.
一切唾手可得
And it's here right in front of you.
最崇高的艺术就是给人带去欢乐 - P·T·巴纳姆